{"data":[{"question":"The police suspect him of ________ stolen goods.","a":"to try to sell","b":"try to sell","c":"trying selling","d":"trying to sell","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Suspect somebody of doing sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"37-year-old Timothy Lindlaw is now designing ________ for offices.","a":"furniture","b":"furnitures","c":"some furnitures","d":"a furniture","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A\/an + countable noun and singular noun.\u00a0\n- Furniture: Uncountable noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"After he ________ a highly successful computer business for two years, he started his second business in a small garage.","a":"has run","b":"runs","c":"was running","d":"had run","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense: expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (he started his second business).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"He ________ his first million pounds by the time he was thirty.","a":"has made","b":"used to make","c":"had made","d":"would make","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense: expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (by the time he was thirty).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"After ________ with the workers of his company, he suddenly dismissed them.","a":"quarrel","b":"quarrelling","c":"quarrelled","d":"have quarrelled","answer":"2","explain":"\n- After\/before + Verb-ing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"I had made five million pounds before things ________ to go wrong.","a":"have begun","b":"began","c":"begin","d":"would begin","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Clause (past participle) + before + Clause (past simple)\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"He said that he ________ to call his new company.","a":"had decided","b":"was deciding","c":"decided","d":"has decided","answer":"1","explain":"\n- In reported speech: \n+ If the reporting verb (i.e. said) is in the past, the reported clause will be in a past form. This form is usually one step back into the past from the original. \n+ If simple present, present perfect or the future is used in the reporting verb (i.e. says) the tense is retained.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"They hope that their plan will be a ________.","a":"succeed","b":"successful","c":"succession","d":"success","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A\/an + countable noun and singular noun.\u00a0\n- Succession: the act of taking over an official job or position, or the right to be the next to take it.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"We asked him what countries he ________.","a":"had been visited","b":"had visited","c":"has been visiting","d":"visited","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense: expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (asked).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"_____ composed traditionally has been a subject of debate among scholars.","a":"Were ballads how","b":"Ballads were how they","c":"How ballads that were","d":"How ballads were","answer":"4","explain":"\n- How + S + V: used to ask or talk about the way in which something happens or is done.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"}]}